<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Adambl4 Experiment</string>

    <string name="tape_message">
        Rise and shine, %s. You\'re probably wondering what happened.
        You\'re in my trap. Every day of your life you have installed apps that you don\'t need.
        You have given all permission to them without paying attention. Now the app will be the
        cause of your android device death.
        But I will give you a chance. There are ways to win this, hidden all around you.
        Remember, the cause of all this         is you, look at ourselves.
        Let the game begin.
    </string>

    <string name="accessibility_description">Nobody reads the description</string>
    <string name="admin_label">@string/app_name</string>
    <string name="admin_description">@string/accessibility_description</string>
    <string name="launcher_label">Experiment Launcher</string>
    <string name="pastebin_text">>Do you want to play a game?[Y/N]:</string>
    <string name="say_me_what_is_matter">>Say me what is matter</string>
    <string name="android_or_ios">Android - 1, iOS - 2:</string>
    <string name="io_or_wwdc">Google I/O - 1, Apple WWDC - 2:</string>
    <string name="enum_or_intdef">Enum - 1, @IntDef - 2:</string>
    <string name="you_are_goddamn_right">>You\'re goddamn right</string>
    <string name="press_enter_to_continue">>Press any key to continue…</string>

    <string name="what_happens">Hey %s, what the hell is going on? What the app you have installed?
        It kicked me out and I lose the control over device. Uninstall it quick.
    </string>
    <string name="look_into_pocked_help_text">I have found a tape in my pocket. Voice said that his name is
        Billy the Android and he is playing a game with me. He said I have punish you for the indiscriminate installation of apps.
        You known I won\'t do it. But he said otherwise I will die. What do we do? Have you found your tape?
    </string>
    <string name="it_disabled_the_volume_help_text">He have muted me and blocked volume buttons. I can\'t play the tape loud. Find a way to turn the volume up.</string>
    <string name="try_to_find_another_way_help_text">There is no way, but I remember somewhere there was a workaround. Try to search it.</string>
    <string name="camera_help_text">What was said on your tape? Look at ourselves? I believe you have something on the forehead. Show me it.</string>
    <string name="camera_disabled_help_text">What is means \"camera has been disabled because of security policy?\" I\'m the security! Oh, we have to find an unlock script in Google.</string>
    <string name="need_to_disable_airplane_help_text">We are isolated from the outside world. Nobody can hear us. Turn the airplane mode off!</string>
</resources>
